Welcome to the Everyday Hero Academy first aid course.
Today, we're going to cover a wide range of first aid skills that you can use in
all sorts of situations, from minor scrapes in a non-emergency,
to life-saving actions during a major crisis.
As we go through these modules, I want you to keep one thing in mind.
Communication is key. If you are acting as a caregiver and an incident happens,
your priority is to reach out to the parent or guardian immediately.
To make that easier, it's a great idea to always keep a file with their
emergency contact info right where you can find it.
It is also best practice to document these conversations by keeping a simple
record of what happened and when you spoke to the family.
Most importantly, if you are facing a true medical emergency,
remember the order of operations. Call 911 first,
and then call the parents as soon as it is safe to do so.